So now, let's build a margin error.
那现在 我们来建一个边际误差
Here's our data set twice,
这是同样的两组数据
and this is a boundary line.
这是分界线
And these are the margins.
这是间隔
Now, there's a difference between the model in the left and the model in the right.
现在 左边模型和右边模型的不同之处在于
The model in the left has a very large margin,
左边模型的间隔较大
and the model in the right has a very small margin.
而右图模型的间隔较小
Recall that the margin is the distance between the two lines,
让我们回想一下 间隔指是两条线之间的距离
and we want to turn this margin into
我们想要把间隔转化为一个误差
an error that we can minimize using gradient descent.
我们就可以使用梯度下降法将误差最小化
We're going to cook up a function that gives us a small error for the large margin case,
我们将编写一个函数 使之在间隔大的情况下误差最小
and a large error for the small margin case.
以及在间隔小的情况下误差最大
This is because we want to punish small margins,
这是因为我们想要惩罚较小的间隔
as our goal is to obtain a model that has as large a margin as possible.
以获得一个拥有尽可能大间隔的模型
And you'll be surprised how simple this is.
你将会发现这很简单
Here, we have our line with the two other boundary lines,
这里我们有一条线及另外两条边界线
and the margin is the distance between the two outside lines.
间隔就是外面这两条线之间的距离
Our equation is aligned wx + b = 0,
我们的方程式是 wx+b=0
and the two dotted lines have equations wx + b = 1,
两条虚线的方程是 wx+b=1
and wx + b = -1.
和 wx+b=-1
That is just the way we pick them and so the margin and we'll see
这就是我们选择它们的方式 同样也是选择间隔的方式
this development in the instructor comments is simply 2 divided by
然后像讲师注释里一样 用 2 除以向量 W 的模
the norm of the vector w. Let's remember that the norm of
我们要记住
w is the square root of the sum of the squares of the components of the vector,
向量 w 的模是向量分量 也就是 w1 和 w2
which are W1 and W2.
平方和的平方根
So for this error, let's find something that
接下来 让我们用这个误差
gives us a large value of the margin is small,
找到较小间隔的最大值
and a small value of the margin is large.
以及较大间隔的最小值
Well simple, the norm of w appears in the denominator.
很简单 既然向量 w 的模是分母
So, if we take the norm of w,
那么我们取向量 w 的模
that grows inversely proportional to the margin. Nice, right?
它就应该与间隔呈反比 是不是很棒
As a matter of fact, since I don't like dealing with square roots,
事实上  鉴于我不喜欢平方根
let's take the norm of w squared,
那我们就用向量 w 模的平方
which is actually the sum of the squares of the components of the vector w. In this case,
即向量分量 w 平方的和 在这种情况下
it's W1 squared + W2 squared.
就是 w1 的平方加 w2 的平方
And as we've seen, since W appears here in the denominator,
如我们之前所看到的 w 出现在分母上
then a large margin gives us a small error and a small margin gives us a large error.
因此 较大间隔代表较小误差 而较小间隔则代表较大误差
That is exactly what we wanted.
这恰好就是我们想要的结果
So to clarify things, here's an example.
我们用一个例子来解释
Let's say, W is the vector 34 and our bias is one.
比如 w 是（3,4）我们的偏差是 1
So our equation of the form w1x1 + w2x2 + b = 0,
那我们的方程 w1x1+w2x2+b=0
is going to be 3x1 + 4x2 + 1 = 0,
就变成了 3x1+4x2+1=0
and that's our main line.
这就是我们的主线
And here's a line with these two companions,
它的两侧分别有一根条虚线
the one that gives the equation 3x1 + 4x2 + 1 = 1,
一条线的方程是 3x1+4x2+1=1
and the one that gives 3x1 + 4x2 + 1 = -1.
另外一条是 3x1 + 4x2 + 1 = -1
So now, the error is a norm of w squared,
那么现在 误差是 w 模的平方
which is 3 squared + 4 squared,
即 3 的平方加 4 的平方
which gives us an error of 25.
得出的误差是 25
And the margin is two divided by the norm of w,
而间隔就是 w 的模除以 2
and the norm of w is the square root of 25 which is 5.
而 w 的模是 25 的平方根 即 5
So, the margin is 2/5 and the error is 25.
那么 间隔就是五分之二 误差就是 25
Let's remember these two numbers: error 25 and margin 2/5.
记住这两个数字 误差 25 间隔 2.5
Now, let's look at a very similar example except instead of 341,
现在 让我们来看一个相似的例子
our weights are going to be 682,
数字变成了w=（6,8）而偏差是 2
so our line is going to have the equation: 6x1 + 8x2 + 2 = 0.
因此我们的等式就变成了 6x1+8x2+2=0
And if you notice, that equation is the same as before except multiplied by two.
你会注意到 该等式就是之前等式乘了 2
So, it gives us the same boundary line because when 3x1 + 4x2 + 1 = 0,
因此 我们得出的分界线是一样的 因为当 3x1+4x2+1 等于 0
then 6x1 + 8x2 + 2 is also 0.
6x1+8x2+2 同样也等于 0
But now our dotted lines are closer to each other because now the value is changed.
但现在 我们的两条虚线之间的距离更小了 因为现在数值变了
Before we have 3x1 + 4x2 + 1 = 1.
之前 我们的等式是 3x1+4x2+1 = 1
And now, we have the twice of that equals one,
现在是之前的两倍等于 1
which means 3x1 + 4x2 + 1 is actually a half,
意味着 3x1+4x2+1 是 0.5
which means the line is much closer.
也意味着这条线靠的更近了
It's actually half the distance as before,
距离实际上是之前的一半
and the same thing happens with the line below.
下面这条线同样如此
And our error is a square of the norm of this vector,
我们的误差是该向量模的平方
which is 6 squared plus 8 squared, which is 100.
即 6 的平方加 8 的平方 等于 100
And our distance is going to be two over the norm of w, which is 2/10.
因此我们的距离就是 2 除以向量 w 模的一半 即 2/10
That is the same as 1/5,
等于 1/5
so this is smaller than the previous margin of 2/5.
这比之前的间隔 2/5 小
This is interesting.
这很有趣
Two models give us the same boundary line,
两个模型呈现出同样的分界线
but one of them gives us a larger margin than the other one.
但其中一个的间隔比另一个更大
Here's a summary for our last example.
最后 我们来总结一下这个例子
We have our large margin,
这边的间隔更大 为 2/5
our margin of 2/5 that gives us a small error of 25,
但误差更小 为 25
and our small margin of 2/10,
而这边间隔较小 为 2/10
which is 1/5 gives us a larger error of 100.
即 1/5 但误差较大 为 100
So that is precisely the margin error.
这就是边际误差
It's just the norm of the vector w squared.
即向量 w 模的平方
Which if you think about it,
思考一下你会发现
it is the exact same error that is given by
这和 L2 正则化中的正则化项一样
the regularization term in L2 regularization. Nice, isn't it?
很奇妙 不是吗？